

CONTACT

Adress
Esenler, İstanbul / Turkey

Email tolgakurtulus1@outlook.com

Website
www.canmarketings.com
www.hediyelikkarakalem.com

Phone +90 534 889 0547

Github - Kaggle - Linkedin

EXPERTISE

HTML & CSS

JQuery + JS

React.js + Redux

Bootsrap / Sass / Gulp / Npm ...

Machine Learning

Python / Python OOP

SQL

Django

Data Analysis And Visualization

COMPETITION

Benim İşim Benim Fikrim

Altınbaş University

Project Name: Black Hole Learning
Project Result: Final Position

Tolga Kurtuluş

Front-end & Software Developer



PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

At a time when technology is advancing at such a rapid rate, to aid this growth and to make a difference no matter how small has always been one of my greatest ambitions. I would like to Software become a part of. Knowledge, creativity, skills and experience: these are essential qualities needed to excel in the field of software, hence my desire to develop them to the highest possible level.



EDUCATION

ALTINBAŞ UNIVERSITY BACHELOR'S DEGREE, 2014 -2019
Electrical and Electronics Engineering (English), English
preparation
Istanbul/Turkey



WORK EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Odeon Technology / Istanbul/ March 2021 - Present

- > We use technologies: Html, css, javascript, jquery, react, redux, strapi, jenkins, sass, npm.
- I am working: OdeonBackoffice, B2b Odeon Tours

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Pixelplus Interactive / Istanbul/ November 2019 - March 2021

- We use technologies: Html, css, javascript, jquery angular, pug, sass, npm, gulp, grunt.
- I have worked projects: Yeşilay, Kalkınma Bankası, Ak Yatırım, Körfez Ulaştırma, Petrol Ofisi, Garanti Bankası, Centurion, Amerikanexpress, Albaraka, Emlak Bankası, Kayseri Belediyesi, Bonus Piu, Bkt, Tursab, Tüpraş, Bonus, Deniz Bonus, Tüyap, Zorlu, Gümüşsuyu, Doqu Home, Hes Kablo, Tradeall, Mondi, İstikbal

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

AYNE Ltd. / Istanbul/ June 2017 - August 2019

- We use technologies: Html, css, javascript, jquery
- > I have worked projects: www.ayneplastik.com

Line Follower Robot on Rough Roads

Altınbaş University

Project Name: Falcon

Project Result: Final Position

High Speed Robot

Altınbaş University

Project Name: Falcon

Project Result: Final Position

CERTIFICATES

HTML & CSS
Codecademy

Javascript
 Codecademy

Front End Development

Codecademy

Python
Udemy - Udemy - Udemy

Machine Learning
Udemy

Machine Learning And AI

AWS

REFERENCES

Ramazan Yamaç (Sr. Frontend

Developer)

Pixelplus Interactive

T: +90 537 861 7318

Ömer Acar (Manager)

AYNE Ltd.

T: + 90 551 958 98 76

AWARDS

Yeşilay (2 Awards)

Altın Örümcek / Haziran 2020

Yeşilay (1 Awards)

Interactive Media Awards / Haziran

Petrol Ofisi (Final Pos.)

Altın Örümcek / Haziran 2020

IT ROJECT MANAGER & FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Tunç İnşaat Ltd. / Istanbul/ April 2018 - March 2019

- Design, develop, test and implement data warehouse systems for BI reporting and analysis.
- The site is under development.

JR. IT ROJECT MANAGER & FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Sermakina Ltd. / Istanbul/ September 2015 - May 2017

- Design, develop, test and implement data warehouse systems for BI reporting and analysis.
- ➤ I edit www.sermakine.com

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & Co-Founder

Can Marketings. / Istanbul/ Oct. 2017 - Aug. 2020

- ➤ I write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices (Python, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap, jQuery). I provide for SEO and SEM planning and organization
- I manage all techology, finance, marketing for the company and activities within the marketing department

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & Founder

Hediyelik Karakalem. / Istanbul/ Aug. 2016 - Aug. 2020

- ➤ I write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices (Python, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap, jQuery). I provide for SEO and SEM planning and organization
- > I develop and conceptualize a comprehensive UI/UX design strategy for the brand.
- ➤ I manage all techology, finance, marketing for the company and activities within the marketing department

FULL STACK DEVELOPER & Founder

Red Life Sphere. / Istanbul/ May 2015 - Aug. 2020

- ➤ I write well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices (Python, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Bootstrap, jQuery). I provide for SEO and SEM planning and organization
- I develop and conceptualize a comprehensive UI/UX design strategy for the brand.

INTERNSHIP FOR DATA ENGINEERING

Garanti Technology / Istanbul/ July 2017 - August 2017

INTERNSHIP FOR SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Ptt General Office / Istanbul/ June 2016 - August 2016

INTERNSHIP FOR DATABASE

Boğaziçi Yönetim A.ş / Istanbul/ June 2012 - August 2012